export const allQuestions1 = [
    {
        "questionText": "Was ist 'ich' auf Englisch?",
        "correctAnswer": "I",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["you", "he", "we"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Was ist 'du' auf Englisch?",
        "correctAnswer": "you (singular, informal)",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["he", "she", "they"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Was ist 'er' auf Englisch?",
        "correctAnswer": "he",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["she", "it", "I"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Was ist 'sie' auf Englisch?",
        "correctAnswer": "she",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["he", "it", "you"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Was ist 'es' auf Englisch?",
        "correctAnswer": "it",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["he", "she", "we"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Was ist 'wir' auf Englisch?",
        "correctAnswer": "we",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["you", "they", "I"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Was ist 'ihr' auf Englisch?",
        "correctAnswer": "you (plural, informal)",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["we", "they", "he"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Was ist 'Sie' (plural) auf Englisch?",
        "correctAnswer": "they",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["we", "you", "he"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Was ist 'Sie' (formal) auf Englisch?",
        "correctAnswer": "you (formal)",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["he", "she", "we"]
    }
];

export const allQuestions2 = [
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'human' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "der Mensch",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die Zeit", "das Jahr", "der Tag"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'time' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "die Zeit",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die Sache", "der Weg", "die Hand"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'year' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "das Jahr",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der Freund", "die Frau", "das Kind"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'day' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "der Tag",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die Stadt", "das Haus", "die Schule"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'thing' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "die Sache",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der Lehrer", "die Arbeit", "das Buch"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'way' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "der Weg",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die Familie", "der Kopf", "die Frage"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'hand' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "die Hand",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die Antwort", "der Platz", "die Welt"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'hope' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "die Hoffnung",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der Traum", "die Freiheit", "das Leben"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'friend' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "der Freund",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die Frau", "der Mann", "das Kind"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'woman' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "die Frau",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der Mann", "das Kind", "die Stadt"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'man' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "der Mann",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["das Kind", "die Schule", "die Arbeit"]
    },
];
export const allQuestions3 = [
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'child' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "das Kind",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die Familie", "der Kopf", "die Frage"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'dream' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "der Traum",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die Frage", "das Jahr", "die Zeit"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'city' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "die Stadt",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["das Haus", "die Schule", "der Lehrer"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'house' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "das Haus",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die Familie", "der Freund", "die Zeit"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'school' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "die Schule",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der Lehrer", "die Arbeit", "das Buch"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'teacher' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "der Lehrer",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die Familie", "die Frage", "der Platz"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'work' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "die Arbeit",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["das Buch", "die Zeit", "der Weg"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'book' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "das Buch",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die Familie", "der Kopf", "die Frage"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'family' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "die Familie",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der Freund", "die Stadt", "das Jahr"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'head' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "der Kopf",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die Hand", "die Stimme", "der Platz"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'question' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "die Frage",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die Antwort", "die Zeit", "das Leben"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'answer' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "die Antwort",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die Frage", "der Weg", "die Stimme"]
    },
]
export const allQuestions4 = [

    {
        "questionText": "What is 'place' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "der Platz",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die Welt", "das Jahr", "die Freiheit"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'world' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "die Welt",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["das Leben", "die Zeit", "der Freund"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'life' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "das Leben",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die Liebe", "der Platz", "die Frage"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'love' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "die Liebe",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["das Jahr", "der Kopf", "die Stimme"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'voice' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "die Stimme",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der Weg", "die Frage", "das Buch"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'body' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "der KÃ¶rper",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die Freiheit", "die Zeit", "das Geld"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'success' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "der Erfolg",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die Hoffnung", "das Jahr", "die Frage"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'idea' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "die Idee",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der Freund", "die Frage", "das Jahr"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'water' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "das Wasser",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die Freiheit", "der Platz", "die Zeit"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'health' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "die Gesundheit",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["das Leben", "die Liebe", "der Kopf"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'freedom' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "die Freiheit",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["das Geld", "die Frage", "der Weg"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'money' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "das Geld",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die Zeit", "der Platz", "die Stimme"]
    },
]
export const allQuestions5 = [
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'language' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "die Sprache",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["das Jahr", "der Freund", "die Frage"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'market' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "der Markt",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die Stadt", "das Jahr", "die Freiheit"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'journey' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "die Reise",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der Weg", "das Leben", "die Frage"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'summer' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "der Sommer",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der Winter", "die Zeit", "die Freiheit"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'winter' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "der Winter",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der Sommer", "die Frage", "das Jahr"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'music' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "die Musik",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der Film", "die Kunst", "der Sport"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'film' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "der Film",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die Musik", "die Kunst", "der Sport"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'art' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "die Kunst",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der Sport", "die Freiheit", "das Leben"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'sport' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "der Sport",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die Musik", "der Film", "die Kunst"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'nature' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "die Natur",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["das Wasser", "die Freiheit", "der Platz"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'computer' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "der Computer",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die Technik", "das Jahr", "die Frage"]
    },

    {
        "questionText": "What is 'technology' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "die Technik",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der Computer", "die Freiheit", "das Leben"]
    },



];
export const allQuestions6 = [

    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Mensch'?",
        "correctAnswer": "der",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Zeit'?",
        "correctAnswer": "die",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Jahr'?",
        "correctAnswer": "das",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die", "der"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Tag'?",
        "correctAnswer": "der",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Sache'?",
        "correctAnswer": "die",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Weg'?",
        "correctAnswer": "der",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Hand'?",
        "correctAnswer": "die",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Freund'?",
        "correctAnswer": "der",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Frau'?",
        "correctAnswer": "die",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Mann'?",
        "correctAnswer": "der",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Kind'?",
        "correctAnswer": "das",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die", "der"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Stadt'?",
        "correctAnswer": "die",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der", "das"]
    },
];
export const allQuestions7 = [

    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Haus'?",
        "correctAnswer": "das",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die", "der"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Schule'?",
        "correctAnswer": "die",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Lehrer'?",
        "correctAnswer": "der",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Arbeit'?",
        "correctAnswer": "die",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Buch'?",
        "correctAnswer": "das",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die", "der"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Familie'?",
        "correctAnswer": "die",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Kopf'?",
        "correctAnswer": "der",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Frage'?",
        "correctAnswer": "die",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Antwort'?",
        "correctAnswer": "die",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Platz'?",
        "correctAnswer": "der",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Welt'?",
        "correctAnswer": "die",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der", "das"]
    },
];
export const allQuestions8 = [
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Leben'?",
        "correctAnswer": "das",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die", "der"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Liebe'?",
        "correctAnswer": "die",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Stimme'?",
        "correctAnswer": "die",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'KÃ¶rper'?",
        "correctAnswer": "der",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Idee'?",
        "correctAnswer": "die",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Wasser'?",
        "correctAnswer": "das",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die", "der"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Gesundheit'?",
        "correctAnswer": "die",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Freiheit'?",
        "correctAnswer": "die",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Geld'?",
        "correctAnswer": "das",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die", "der"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Sprache'?",
        "correctAnswer": "die",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Markt'?",
        "correctAnswer": "der",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die", "das"]
    },
];
export const allQuestions9 = [

    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Reise'?",
        "correctAnswer": "die",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Sommer'?",
        "correctAnswer": "der",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Winter'?",
        "correctAnswer": "der",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Musik'?",
        "correctAnswer": "die",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Film'?",
        "correctAnswer": "der",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Kunst'?",
        "correctAnswer": "die",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Sport'?",
        "correctAnswer": "der",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Natur'?",
        "correctAnswer": "die",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Computer'?",
        "correctAnswer": "der",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Technik'?",
        "correctAnswer": "die",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Erfolg'?",
        "correctAnswer": "der",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Hoffnung'?",
        "correctAnswer": "die",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["der", "das"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What article is 'Traum'?",
        "correctAnswer": "der",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["die", "das"]
    }



];
export const allQuestions10 =
    [
        {
            "questionText": "Was ist 'Mensch' auf Englisch?",
            "correctAnswer": "human",
            "incorrectAnswers": ["time", "year", "day"]
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Was ist 'Zeit' auf Englisch?",
            "correctAnswer": "time",
            "incorrectAnswers": ["thing", "way", "hand"]
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Was ist 'Jahr' auf Englisch?",
            "correctAnswer": "year",
            "incorrectAnswers": ["friend", "woman", "man"]
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Was ist 'Tag' auf Englisch?",
            "correctAnswer": "day",
            "incorrectAnswers": ["city", "house", "school"]
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Was ist 'Sache' auf Englisch?",
            "correctAnswer": "thing",
            "incorrectAnswers": ["family", "head", "question"]
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Was ist 'Weg' auf Englisch?",
            "correctAnswer": "way",
            "incorrectAnswers": ["hand", "friend", "woman"]
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Was ist 'Freund' auf Englisch?",
            "correctAnswer": "friend",
            "incorrectAnswers": ["child", "teacher", "work"]
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Was ist 'Frau' auf Englisch?",
            "correctAnswer": "woman",
            "incorrectAnswers": ["man", "child", "city"]
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Was ist 'Kind' auf Englisch?",
            "correctAnswer": "child",
            "incorrectAnswers": ["family", "head", "question"]
        },
    ];
export const allQuestions11 = [
    {
        "questionText": "Was ist 'Stadt' auf Englisch?",
        "correctAnswer": "city",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["house", "school", "friend"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Was ist 'Haus' auf Englisch?",
        "correctAnswer": "house",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["book", "family", "time"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Was ist 'Buch' auf Englisch?",
        "correctAnswer": "book",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["work", "friend", "city"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Was ist 'Arbeit' auf Englisch?",
        "correctAnswer": "work",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["time", "thing", "way"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Was ist 'Kopf' auf Englisch?",
        "correctAnswer": "head",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["hand", "body", "friend"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Was ist 'Frage' auf Englisch?",
        "correctAnswer": "question",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["answer", "time", "place"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Was ist 'Antwort' auf Englisch?",
        "correctAnswer": "answer",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["question", "friend", "city"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Was ist 'Welt' auf Englisch?",
        "correctAnswer": "world",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["life", "time", "place"]
    }
]
export const allQuestions12 = [
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'to be' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "sein",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["haben", "gehen", "essen"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'to have' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "haben",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["sein", "gehen", "trinken"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'to go' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "gehen",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["sehen", "essen", "lesen"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'to eat' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "essen",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["trinken", "schlafen", "fahren"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'to drink' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "trinken",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["essen", "lesen", "gehen"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'to sleep' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "schlafen",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["essen", "fahren", "arbeiten"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'to drive' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "fahren",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["gehen", "sehen", "essen"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'to work' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "arbeiten",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["schlafen", "lesen", "trinken"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'to read' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "lesen",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["sehen", "essen", "fahren"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'to see' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "sehen",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["lesen", "essen", "arbeiten"]
    },
];

export const allQuestions13 = [
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'to speak' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "sprechen",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["hÃ¶ren", "sehen", "essen"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'to hear' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "hÃ¶ren",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["essen", "gehen", "arbeiten"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'to give' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "geben",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["nehmen", "lesen", "fahren"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'to take' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "nehmen",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["geben", "sehen", "essen"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'to run' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "laufen",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["gehen", "fahren", "lesen"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'to come' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "kommen",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["gehen", "sehen", "essen"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'to stand' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "stehen",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["sitzen", "essen", "fahren"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'to sit' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "sitzen",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["stehen", "essen", "sehen"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'to write' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "schreiben",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["lesen", "sehen", "gehen"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'to live' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "leben",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["arbeiten", "sehen", "essen"]
    },
];

export const allQuestions14 = [
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'to find' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "finden",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["verlieren", "sehen", "gehen"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'to ask' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "fragen",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["antworten", "sehen", "lesen"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'to answer' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "antworten",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["fragen", "sehen", "gehen"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'to buy' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "kaufen",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["verkaufen", "sehen", "gehen"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'to sell' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "verkaufen",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["kaufen", "sehen", "essen"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'to bring' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "bringen",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["nehmen", "gehen", "sehen"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'to help' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "helfen",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["sehen", "essen", "gehen"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'to show' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "zeigen",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["sehen", "essen", "laufen"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'to listen' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "zuhÃ¶ren",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["sehen", "essen", "trinken"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'to play' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "spielen",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["sehen", "gehen", "essen"]
    },
];
export const allQuestions15 = [
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'big' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "groÃ",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["klein", "schÃ¶n", "lang"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'small' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "klein",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["groÃ", "schnell", "dunkel"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'beautiful' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "schÃ¶n",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["hÃ¤sslich", "lang", "hell"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'ugly' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "hÃ¤sslich",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["schÃ¶n", "dunkel", "schnell"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'fast' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "schnell",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["langsam", "hell", "klein"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'slow' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "langsam",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["schnell", "groÃ", "hell"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'dark' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "dunkel",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["hell", "groÃ", "schnell"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'light' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "hell",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["dunkel", "lang", "klein"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'long' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "lang",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["kurz", "groÃ", "klein"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'short' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "kurz",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["lang", "groÃ", "hell"]
    },
];

export const allQuestions16 = [
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'young' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "jung",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["alt", "schÃ¶n", "klein"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'old' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "alt",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["jung", "groÃ", "hell"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'rich' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "reich",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["arm", "dunkel", "schnell"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'poor' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "arm",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["reich", "schnell", "hell"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'happy' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "glÃ¼cklich",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["traurig", "alt", "groÃ"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'sad' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "traurig",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["glÃ¼cklich", "jung", "hell"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'strong' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "stark",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["schwach", "dunkel", "klein"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'weak' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "schwach",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["stark", "groÃ", "schnell"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'easy' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "einfach",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["schwierig", "langsam", "hell"]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is 'difficult' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "schwierig",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["einfach", "dunkel", "klein"]
    },
];
export const allQuestions17 = [
    {
        "questionText": "Which is the correct word order for the sentence: 'I go to school' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "Ich gehe zur Schule.",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["Zur Schule gehe ich.", "Ich zur Schule gehe.", "Gehe ich zur Schule."]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Which is the correct word order for the sentence: 'She eats an apple' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "Sie isst einen Apfel.",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["Einen Apfel isst sie.", "Sie einen Apfel isst.", "Isst sie einen Apfel."]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Which is the correct word order for the sentence: 'We are playing soccer' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "Wir spielen FuÃball.",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["FuÃball spielen wir.", "Wir FuÃball spielen.", "Spielen wir FuÃball."]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Which is the correct word order for the sentence: 'They read a book' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "Sie lesen ein Buch.",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["Ein Buch lesen sie.", "Sie ein Buch lesen.", "Lesen sie ein Buch."]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Which is the correct word order for the sentence: 'I have a dog' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "Ich habe einen Hund.",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["Einen Hund habe ich.", "Ich einen Hund habe.", "Habe ich einen Hund."]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Which is the correct word order for the sentence: 'You are working' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "Du arbeitest.",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["Arbeitest du.", "Du arbeiten bist.", "Bist du arbeiten."]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Which is the correct word order for the sentence: 'He is studying German' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "Er studiert Deutsch.",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["Deutsch studiert er.", "Er Deutsch studiert.", "Studiert er Deutsch."]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Which is the correct word order for the sentence: 'We are eating pizza' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "Wir essen Pizza.",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["Pizza essen wir.", "Wir Pizza essen.", "Essen wir Pizza."]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Which is the correct word order for the sentence: 'They are coming tomorrow' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "Sie kommen morgen.",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["Morgen kommen sie.", "Sie morgen kommen.", "Kommen sie morgen."]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Which is the correct word order for the sentence: 'I want to drink coffee' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "Ich will Kaffee trinken.",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["Kaffee trinken ich will.", "Ich Kaffee trinken will.", "Will ich Kaffee trinken."]
    },
];

export const allQuestions18 = [
    {
        "questionText": "Which is the correct word order for the sentence: 'She likes reading books' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "Sie liest gerne BÃ¼cher.",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["Gerne liest sie BÃ¼cher.", "Sie BÃ¼cher liest gerne.", "Liest sie gerne BÃ¼cher."]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Which is the correct word order for the sentence: 'I am at the bus stop' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "Ich bin an der Bushaltestelle.",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["An der Bushaltestelle bin ich.", "Ich an der Bushaltestelle bin.", "Bin ich an der Bushaltestelle."]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Which is the correct word order for the sentence: 'You have a question' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "Du hast eine Frage.",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["Eine Frage du hast.", "Du eine Frage hast.", "Hast du eine Frage."]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Which is the correct word order for the sentence: 'We are watching a movie' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "Wir schauen einen Film.",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["Einen Film schauen wir.", "Wir einen Film schauen.", "Schauen wir einen Film."]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Which is the correct word order for the sentence: 'They play tennis every Sunday' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "Sie spielen jeden Sonntag Tennis.",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["Jeden Sonntag Tennis spielen sie.", "Sie Tennis spielen jeden Sonntag.", "Spielen sie jeden Sonntag Tennis."]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Which is the correct word order for the sentence: 'I live in Berlin' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "Ich wohne in Berlin.",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["In Berlin wohne ich.", "Ich in Berlin wohne.", "Wohne ich in Berlin."]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Which is the correct word order for the sentence: 'We are going to the park' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "Wir gehen in den Park.",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["In den Park gehen wir.", "Gehen wir in den Park.", "Wir in den Park gehen."]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Which is the correct word order for the sentence: 'He works at a school' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "Er arbeitet in einer Schule.",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["In einer Schule arbeitet er.", "Er in einer Schule arbeitet.", "Arbeitet er in einer Schule."]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Which is the correct word order for the sentence: 'I am reading a book' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "Ich lese ein Buch.",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["Ein Buch lese ich.", "Ich ein Buch lese.", "Lese ich ein Buch."]
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Which is the correct word order for the sentence: 'They speak German' in German?",
        "correctAnswer": "Sie sprechen Deutsch.",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["Deutsch sprechen sie.", "Sie Deutsch sprechen.", "Sprechen sie Deutsch."]
    },
];
